[Music]
our heartest congratulations to team mg
for achieving this 100 existance clearly
a century is a mous milestone which will
always be cherished I think the
achievements a two Testament of
Automotive Excellence passion and
Innovation uh in the automotive space
which has been shown by team mg we are
very proud to be associated with Team mg
in their insurance program I think this
relationship is based on shared value of
customer Simplicity Innovation and
passion and I'm sure as you move ahead
in times this relationship will go from
strength to strength in bringing new
products for the customers and also for
the channel partners of
mg teach years
wel